见鬼  亚哈  我还想睡觉呢
Damn it, Ahab, I'm trying to sleep!
怎么了  孩子
What is it, boy?
什么都没有啊
There's nothing out there.
天呐
Oh, my god.
你觉得顺利吗
How do you think it went?
我们很快就会知道了
Well, we'll find out soon enough.
两位我最喜欢的红发妹子
Ah, my two favorite redheads.
你们来干什么
And what are you doing?
我们想知道你的周年纪念过得如何
We wanted to know how your anniversary went.
我们为两种结果都做了准备
And we came prepared either way.
不论是眼泪
Tears or...
还是干杯
Cheers!
是哪种  孩子
Which one is it, kiddo?
两位  昨晚很棒
Guys, it was great.
我所谓的很棒  是指经过了这几周
And when I say "great," I mean, after the last few weeks,
已经很不错了
it was great.
那么你和贝克特是又在一起了吗
So does this mean you and Beckett are back together?
我们...有进展了
This means, uh, we're making progress.
我会维持这份好运
And I'm gonna, you know, keep the mojo going
继续想办法参与她的凶案
by wriggling my way into her homicide cases.
你们好啊
Hello, all.
早上好
Ah, good morning.
看看是谁来了
Oh, well, look who's here!
很高兴你答应为理查德做顾问
Ooh, I am so glad you agreed to consult with Richard.
或许这钱坑现在可以开始获利了
Maybe now this money pit will turn a profit.
什么  妈妈
W-what was that, mother?
看看这时间啊
Oh, look at the time.
我们得走了  亲爱的
We have to go, darling.
理查德
Oh, Richard.
-我真替你和凯瑟琳高兴  -谢谢
- I am so pleased about you and Katherine. - Thank you.
-别搞砸了  -谢谢
- Try not to blow it. - Thank you.
恭喜  爸爸
Congrats, dad.
谢谢
Thank you.
回头见
See you later.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye!
-你为什么对她们撒谎  -我没有
- Why are you lying to them? - I'm n--
我没有对她们撒谎
I'm not lying to them.
好啊  那你告诉她们
Oh, good, so you did tell them
你俩的周年纪念中途中断了
that your anniversary was cut short
因为贝克特收到了一则神秘短信
when Beckett received a mystery text.
我可能没提那部分
I might have left that part out.
你是不是还忘了提
Oh, did you also maybe leave out
你叫我今早过来
the part where you asked me to come in this morning
好黑入贝克特的手机
in order to hack Beckett's cellphone
查明短信是谁发的
to tell you who sent her that text?
好吧  我知道这看上去什么样
Okay, I know how that looks, but
但贝克特肯定有事
something is going on with Beckett,
我担心她
and I-I-I'm worried about her.
我知道
I know.
好吧  你去做你该做的
Okay, you go do what you need to do.
我看看能查到什么
I'll see what I can find out.
好
Okay.
那个  海莉
You know, Hayley,
我为你布置了一下接待处对面的
I set up the small office on the other side of reception
那间小房间
especially for you.
我在这儿就行啦
I'm good here.
这是我的办公室啊
But this is my office.
当然是了
Of course it is.
如果我有发现一定告诉你
I shall call you if I find anything out.
今天愉快
Have a good day.
维克拉姆
Uh, Vikram?
惊喜
Surprise!
欢迎来到我们的新办公室
Welcome to our new office.
脱衣舞俱乐部  不是吧
A strip club? Really?
你叫我找一个
Hey, you said to find a location
我们可以用来查洛克塞特的地方
where we could hunt for LokSat
而且完全不会被人监视
without anyone looking over our shoulders.
这就是你能找到的最好的地方吗
Yeah, and, uh, this is the best you could find?
多棒啊  风化组查抄了这里
It's perfect. Vice raided the place.
现在因审判而闲置
Now it's tied up in trial.
我们可以在这里工作数月  完全不会被发现
We can operate here for months completely off the grid.
再有  我也可以练练舞步
Plus, I can work out my core.
昨晚的短信  你发现了什么
So, the text from last night. What did you find?
其实
Actually, uh...
那个线索无果
that's a dead end.
-什么  -抱歉
- What? - My bad.
你昨晚不知道吗
A-and you didn't know this last night?
你给我发短信就是为了打断我和卡塞尔的
Did you text me to pull me out of my anniversary dinner
周年纪念晚宴吗
with Castle?
听我说  你跟他分手是有原因的
Look, you broke up with him for a reason.
绝不能让任何人知道我们在做什么  尤其卡塞尔
No one can know what we're doing, especially Castle.
-这太危险了  -我知道
- It's too dangerous. - I know.
我已经格外小心了
And I am being extremely careful.
我只是想尽量不因此毁了我的婚姻
I'm just trying not to lose my marriage in the process.
好的  停尸房见
Okay, I'll meet you at the morgue.
79街船坞发现一具浮尸
They found a floater at the 79th street boat basin.
我得走了
I got to go.
还挺合适的
Oddly validating.
帕穆特
Yo, Perlmutter.
你现在要完全走颓废风了啊
Oh, so you're going full hipster now.
你开始腌手工咸菜了吗
Yeah, have you started jarring artisanal pickles yet?
你们还带着段子而来  真好
Ah, you've come bearing jokes. Wonderful.
确认身份了吗
So, we get an I.D. yet?
没有  是位无名氏
Uh, no. She's a Jane Doe.
20多  接触性枪伤
20s, contact gunshot wound.
看来她是以枪决形式被杀
Looks like she was killed execution style,
然后被弃尸水中
then dumped in the water.
听上去像黑帮干的
Sounds like a mob hit.
谁啊  阿尔·卡彭吗
From who? Al capone?
那是一条20年代的裙子
That dress is straight out of the '20s.
这是戏服  警探
Uh, it's a costume, detective.
"标志邮轮公司物品"
"Property of Iconic Cruise Lines."
那么无名氏
So, our Jane Doe
一定是邮轮上的表演者
must have been a cruise-ship entertainer.
那么她可能是死在
So she could have been killed aboard
大西洋任何一艘船上
any ship in the Atlantic
然后随海流漂了过来
and drifted here on the currents.
或许不是  尸体漂白
Or not. Based on the modest level
和浮肿程度并不重
of blanching and bloating,
她的尸体入睡还不到10到12小时
her body's been in the water less than 10 to 12 hours.
那么她所乘的船可能还在附近
So whatever boat she was on could still be nearby.
-各位  我们先...  -等等
- You know what, guys, let's start with... - Now, hold on.
有段牙线
Some kind of floss...
系在后臼齿上了
...tied to her back molar...
一直深入她喉咙里
...going down her throat.
如果这是我想的那个东西
If that's what I think it is,
这位无名氏可能还兼职做偷运
this Jane Doe could have had a little side business smuggling.
邮轮是贩卖毒品的好地方
A cruise ship is a good place to sell drugs.
国际港口  很不错的客户群
International ports, a captive customer base.
或许她被卷入了船上的地盘战
Maybe she got involved in a little on-board turf war,
对手干掉了她
and the competition took her out.
但为什么只有一包啊
Except why just one bag?
如果她真是毒贩
I mean, if she was an actual mule,
-我们该拉出20包才对  -至少
- we'd be pulling out 20 of those. - At least.
我会让实验室加急检测一下
I'll put a rush on this at the lab.
现在  我们去查查
Meanwhile, we need to figure out
无名氏原来是在哪艘标志邮轮上
which Iconic Cruise Ship our Jane Doe was on,
那是犯罪现场
because that's our crime scene.
我刚跟标志邮轮公司通过电话
I just got off the phone with Iconic Cruise Lines.
被害人叫劳拉·麦登
Our victim is Lara Madden.
是舞剧《地下酒吧》的一位舞者
She was a dancer in their show called "Speakeasy."
昨晚还进行过表演
Apparently she performed in it last night.
那怪不得穿成那样
Okay, well, that - explains the flapper dress.
她所工作的船
And the boat she worked on
是一艘老式泰坦尼克号年代主题的远洋油轮
is an old "Titanic"-era-themed oceanliner
本特利皇家邮轮
bamed the RMS Bently.
破晓时停靠进了曼哈顿邮轮码头
It put into port at Manhattan Cruise Terminal at dawn.
密歇根人
Michigan I.D.?
联络亲属了吗
You contact her next-of-kin?
嗯  她妈妈今天晚些时候会飞来
Yeah, her mother is flying in later today.
她说劳拉
She said that Lara
辞去了一家环境非盈利机构的职位
quit her job at an environmental nonprofit
就为去邮轮上工作
in order to work on the cruise line,
好帮助家人还债
all to help her family get out of debt.
帕穆特刚刚打来了
Perlmutter just called.
劳拉胃里的那个包
Turns out that baggie from Lara's stomach...
-是高纯海洛因  -高纯
- pure uncut heroin. - Uncut?
怪不得她只吞了一包
No wonder she only swallowed one baggie.
那一小袋价值三万呢
That 8-ball has a street value of $30k.
高纯海洛因都直接来自毒品集团
Uncut heroin - comes directly from the cartel,
一个密歇根来的舞者是怎么拿到的
so how does a dancer from Michigan get her hands on that?
或许是船上任何人给的
It could have came from anybody on the ship.
问题是  我们的嫌疑人
The problem is, all of our suspects
今早都下船了
disembarked this morning.
嗯  两千人呢
Yeah, like 2,000 of them.
而且可能去了全城各处
They're probably all over the city
或者现在已经飞了回去
or flying back to wherever they came from by now.
你们查查乘客和
Okay, why don't you guys run the names
船员名单
from all the passenger and crew manifests?
看看有没有什么结果
See if anything pops.
我去船上
I'll head off to the ship,
看能不能找到犯罪现场
see if I can find an actual crime scene.
标志公司以两件事为傲
Here at Iconic, we pride ourselves on two things--
老式海洋旅行的优雅
The old-world elegance of ocean travel
和我们完美的安全记录
and our impeccable safety record.
所以不管劳拉遭遇了什么事
So I'm sure whatever happened to Lara
肯定只是一起不幸事故
was simply a tragic accident.
她头部中枪
Uh, well, she was shot in the head,
除非她是绊倒摔在了一颗子弹上
so unless she tripped and fell on a bullet,
那就不是意外
it wasn't an accident.
我以为你们的乘客
Now, I thought that all of your passengers
今早都下船了呢
disembarked this morning.
那是一些长期住在船上的旅客
Oh, those are some - of the ship's resident guests,
大都是退休人士  常年住在船上
mostly retirees - who live aboard year-round.
有一些旅客  比如尼尔森姐妹
Some of them, like the Nelson sisters,
在船上待的时间比大部分船员都久
have been on the ship longer than most of the crew.
我们叫她们"八卦天后"
We call them "The gossip girls."
抱歉  我得接一下
Um, I-I'm sorry, I have to get this.
当然
Oh, sure thing.
维克拉姆  有什么发现
Hey, Vikram, what do you got?
我们找到了金矿
We hit the mother lode.
我查了被害人胃里的那份海洛因
I ran the heroin found in our victim's stomach.
贝克特  与瓦肯·西蒙斯
Beckett, it's an exact 100% match
所出售的海洛因完全匹配
to the heroin Vulcan Simmons was selling.
那么杀劳拉的凶手
So Lara's killer is linked
跟接管了瓦肯毒品交易的人有关
to whoever took over Vulcan's drug pipeline.
这就是我们一直在等的
This is it... what we've been waiting for.
你能相信居然来自我们自己的案件吗
And do you believe it came from one of our own cases?
好了  我们得小心
Okay, we have to be careful.
我们不能让人知道我们知情  暴露身份
We can't let on that we know anything and blow our cover.
-而且不仅是中情局里的那个目标  -嗯
- And I'm not just talking about the target in the CIA. - Yeah.
-幸好卡塞尔这次没在  -是啊
- Good thing Castle's nowhere near this one. - Yeah.
嘿
Ahoy!
我是世界之王[出自《泰坦尼克号》]
I'm the king of the world!
喂  贝克特
Hello? Beckett?
这不是真的
This can't be happening.
你是怎么上船的
How did you get on board?
我们一直在谈论要买艘船
You know, we always talked about buying a boat.
你觉得呢  我知道需要修补一下
What do you think? I mean, I know it's a fixer-upper.
不知道  结婚两周年再买吧
I don't know -- maybe for our second anniversary.
我觉得没什么能跟第一年这次相比
Oh, I don't know if anything's gonna compare to the first.
你真的不应该来这儿
You know, you really shouldn't be here.
为什么
Why not?
船开了吗
Are we moving?
贝克特  犯罪现场貌似是想逃跑
Beckett, I think your crime scene's making a run for it.
船长  你得把船停下
Captain, you need to stop this ship.
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
船长  我们正在调查
Captain, we're investigating the murder
你船上一名舞者被杀的案子
of one of your ship's dancers.
总部命令我出港
I'm under orders from headquarters to get under way.
你是说标志邮轮公司
Are you telling me that Iconic Cruise Lines
想要掩盖这起凶杀案吗
is trying to cover up the murder?
跟你这么说吧  公司快要破产了
I'm telling you the company's near bankruptcy.
不能再有负面新闻了
They can't afford the bad press.
立刻停船  否则我会起诉你妨碍司法
Stop this ship, or I will charge you with obstruction.
我可以让海岸警卫队禁止这艘船航行
I can call the coast guard to interdict this vessel.
你当然可以
Sure, you can.
不过咱俩都清楚
But you know as well as I do
等到他们出动的时候
that by the time you activate them,
我们就已经到公海了
we'll be in international waters.
那里不受美国法律的约束
Where U.S. laws don't apply.
标志公司就打的这个盘算
That's what Iconic is counting on.
告诉你们俩一声
Oh, and just so the two of you know,
大约一个小时后会有艘船来接你们
they're sending a boat to pick you up in about an hour.
这么说我们只有60分钟的时间
So we've got 60 minutes to investigate this murder
在犯罪现场进行调查了
before we lose access to our crime scene.
-关于这个  -不是吧
- And about that... - Really?
上面命令我要求船员
I've been instructed to order the crew
不许跟你们配合
not to cooperate with you.
我可不要因为这事而丢了饭碗
Hey, I'm not losing my job over this.
我们得分头行动
We got to divide and conquer.
没错  我去跟劳拉的舞者朋友们谈谈
Right. I'll talk to Lara's dancer friends.
她们可能是最后见到她的人
They may be the last ones to see her alive.
好的  可你要记住  她们不会配合我们的
Okay, but just remember, they're not supposed to cooperate,
所以别告诉她们你是帮警察工作的
So don't tell them that you're working with the police.
那你去哪
Where will you be?
游泳池甲板上有三个玛莎那样的人
There are three Marthas on lido deck.
如果有人对这艘船很了解
If anyone knows anything about this ship,
那一定就是她们了
it's gonna be them.
况且  她们也不是船员
And plus, they're not with the crew.
好吧  如果她们像我母亲
All right, if they're anything like my mother,
那你一定会忙不过来的
you're gonna have your hands full.
好了  注意一下
Okay, heads-up.
有个有钱人买下了下次巡航的
So, some rich guy bought the "be part of the show"
参与舞蹈大礼包
dance package for our next cruise.
我保证不踩到别人的脚
And I promise not to step on anyone's toes.
你是席尔默先生吗
Are you Mr. Schirmer?
是的  我早上船了
Yeah, I boarded early
希望能多参与一下排练
in hopes of getting a little extra rehearsal time.
我不知道你是怎么早上船的  席尔默先生
Well, I'm not sure how you boarded early, Mr. Schirmer,
-可是我们  -其实席尔默先生是我父亲
- But we're... - Please, actually, Mr. Schirmer is my father.
请叫我
Please call me...
杰瑞...皮
Jermphld...
不好意思  我没听清
I'm sorry, what?
Jermphld
Jermphld.
-戴夫  -听候吩咐
- Dave? - At your service.
戴夫  很抱歉  排练不包括在舞蹈礼包内
Well, Dave, I'm sorry, rehearsal's not part of the dance package.
这样吧  我再多加100块钱
I'll tell you what -- there's an extra $100 in it for you.
各就各位
Places, everyone.
我要热一热身
I'm gonna warm up a little bit.
我想  好吧
I thought -- okay, gotcha.
我一个朋友
You know, a friend of mine
大约一个月前也买了舞蹈礼包
bought the dance package on a cruise about a month ago.
他说有个舞者叫劳拉
He said there was a dancer here by the name of Lara
对他很有帮助  她今天在吗
who was very helpful -- is she here today?
劳拉今天没来
Actually, Lara's a no-show for today.
可如果你想要见她的话
But if you want to meet her,
你可以去问问她的铺友贝瑟尼
you can ask her bunkmate, Bethany.
谢谢
Thank you.
戴夫  你所填的调查表上说
So, Dave, according to your questionnaire,
你以前是专业的舞蹈演员  对吧
you have professional dance experience, right?
是的  是的  没错
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
你也学习了我们发给你的视频吗
And you studied the video we sent?
-是的  当然  -很好
- Yes, of course. - Perfect.
那我们就从开场舞蹈开始吧
So let's take it from the opening number.
开场舞蹈
Opening number.
打扰一下  贝瑟尼  我
Excuse me, Bethany? I --
位置不错
Oh, Good spot.
好了
Okay.
我们从头开始
Let's take this from the top, people.
面朝舞台后面
We face upstage.
后面
Upstage.
-谢谢  谢谢  -5  6  7  8
- Thank you, thank you. - A-5, 6, 7, 8.
走起  扭屁股  左边  右边
And walk. And hip. And left and right.
转一圈  三人一组
And traveling. And trio.
转屁股  踢腿
And hip circle, flick.
很好  准备好劈腿
Here we go, and ready for the dance break.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
1  2  3  4  5  6  7  8
1, 2, 3, 4. 5, 6, 7, 8.
打开膝盖  收起
Knees out, in.
打开  摆手
Out, flick.
打开  收起  打开  摆手
Out, in. Out, flick.
-爵士手型  -没错
- Jazz hands. - That's right.
很好  很好
Yes! There you go.
走到舞台左边
Traveling stage left.
没错  步态舞
And here we go. Cakewalk.
很棒  戴夫
Nice, Dave.
很好
Good.
准备托起
Ready for the big lift up!
劳拉很踏实
Lara's down-to-earth.
不像其他的舞者那么高高自大
Not full of herself like some of those other dancers.
可上次不是
Oh, except for the last trip.
她有点心不在焉
I mean, she was distracted.
天哪  她都没空跟我们聊天了
Boy, she didn't have time for our chats.
可能她认识了新朋友
Well, maybe she met someone new.
你为什么这么想知道劳拉的事
Why do you want to know so much about Lara?
她遇到什么麻烦了吗
Is she in some kind of trouble?
她的名字出现在了一个案子中  我想查明
Her name came up in a case, and I'm trying to figure out
她是不是跟船上的某个
if she was involved with anyone
贩毒的人有关系
on board connected to drugs.
反正我不知道
Not that I know of.
伊莲
Elaine?
你有什么想告诉我的吗
Is there something you want to let me know?
你又嗑了吗
Are you toking again?
好吧  我嗑了
All right, yes.
我是从艾萨克那弄到的大麻  抓我吧
And I score my weed from Isaac, arrest me.
不要  千万别抓我
No, please, don't arrest me.
-不不不  艾萨克是谁  -艾萨克·邓恩
- No, no, no. Who's isaac? - Isaac Dern.
他是船上的调酒师  而且我非常确定
He's a bartender on board, and I'm pretty sure
他和劳拉喜欢一起玩
that he and Lara like to hang out together.
艾萨克·邓恩
Isaac Dern...
有因吸毒和持有武器被捕的记录
history of drug and weapon arrests.
而且他在塔尔萨还有张未执行的逮捕令
Plus he's got an outstanding warrant in Tulsa.
他能去世界各地的港口
Well, with access to ports around the world,
他可能跟贩毒集团有关系  偷运纯海洛因
he could be tapped into cartels moving uncut heroin.
这可能就是我们要找的人
This could be our guy.
好吧  谢了  莱恩
All right, thanks, Ryan.
不客气
You bet.
艾萨克·邓恩
Isaac Dern?
我是贝克特警监  12分局的
Captain Beckett, 12th Precinct.
上级严格命令我不能跟警察谈
I have strict orders not to talk to the cops.
好吧  你可以不跟我谈
Okay, fine. You don't have to talk to me.
我让国际刑警来抓你
I'll just have Interpol pick you up
你有张还未执行的逮捕令
on your outstanding warrant
他们可以在下个港口逮捕你  然后我们再谈
at your next port of call, and we can talk then.
好吧  你想知道什么
Okay, what do you want to know?
告诉我你跟劳拉·麦登的关系
Tell me about your relationship with Lara Madden.
我们只是朋友  怎么了
We're just friends. Why?
她死了
She's dead.
她的尸体昨晚被冲上岸了
Her body washed up last night.
她是不是偷了你的毒品  所以你才杀了她
Did she steal your drugs? Is that why you killed her?
等等  你在说什么啊
Wait, what are you talking about?
我们知道你在贩毒
We know you deal drugs.
我们在她的体内发现了高纯海洛因
We found your uncut heroin on her body.
等等  我是卖大麻的
Slow down -- I sell weed.
那你的上家呢
And what about the people that you work for?
我是从各个港口的小毒贩那里进货
I get my product from petty dealers at the ports.
我没加入什么组织  更没杀劳拉  我发誓
I'm not tapped in. And I didn't kill Lara, I swear.
昨晚你在哪
Where were you last night?
一直在这待到凌晨三点
Here until 3:00 A.M.,
给一群喝醉的游客调鸡尾酒
serving cocktails to a bunch of drunk tourists.
等等  可我在劳拉表演完后见到过她
Wait, but I did see Lara after her show
大约在昨晚11点左右
around 11:00 last night.
她还穿着表演服
She was still dressed in her costume,
急着去救生艇甲板
rushing to the boat deck.
有人跟她一起吗
Was she with anyone?
我没看见
Not that I could see.
准备好再来一遍了吗  戴夫
You ready to go again, Dave?
-我们休息五分钟  -休息五分钟
- Let's take five, people. - Take five, people.
听说你是  劳拉的铺友
So, you're, Lara's roommate.
你不是说你当过职业舞蹈演员吗
Thought you said you had professional dancing experience.
是的  跳的是方块舞
Yeah, I was a professional square dancer.
没这么累
A lot less cardio.
真好
Great.
听我说  我不是什么戴夫·席尔默
Listen, I'm not really Dave Schirmer.
我是跟纽约警局合作的私家侦探
I'm a private investigator working with the NYPD.
很遗憾的通知你劳拉被杀了
I'm sorry to tell you Lara's been murdered.
被杀  等等  你说什么
Murdered? Wait, what?
你知道她跟船上的什么人有矛盾吗
Do you know if she had a problem with anyone on the ship?
-我不知道  -好吧
- I don't think so. - Okay.
-她最近有什么不寻常的举动吗  -有
- Had she been acting unusually recently? - Yeah.
最近  劳拉空闲的时候
Lately, Lara was spending a lot of her free time
都在下层甲板轮机室
below decks in engineering.
-你知道为什么吗  -她不肯说
- Do you know why? - She wouldn't talk about it.
我能不能去一下你们的舱房
Can I go down to your bunk
看一下劳拉的东西
just to look through Lara's things,
看看她有没有日记什么的
see if she had a diary or anything
能帮我们找到她的凶手
that might help find her killer.
就算劳拉写日记
If Lara had a diary,
她也绝不会放在我们舱房里
the last place she would keep it is in our bunk.
这艘破船上经常有人偷东西
Things get stolen all the time on this raggedy ship.
我们都有秘密藏东西的地方
We all have secret stash spots.
有些地方你根本想不到
Some of them are pretty creative.
你知道劳拉把东西藏在哪吗
Do you have any idea where Lara's stash spot was?
抱歉
Sorry.
谢谢你的帮助
Thank you for your help.
有进展吗
Get anything?
腹股沟拉伤  还有条潜在的线索
A pulled groin and a potential clue.
劳拉经常去下层甲板轮机室
Lara spent a lot of time below decks in engineering.
你呢
How about you?
一个酒保昨晚表演结束后
A bartender saw Lara after the show last night
看见劳拉站在23号支架旁
standing by the gantry 23.
也许她去和做毒品交易的人碰面但出了问题
Maybe she met someone for a drug deal and things went sideways.
也许她被人跟踪了
Or maybe she was being followed.
不管怎样  我要去救生艇甲板上看看
Either way, I'm going down to the boat deck,
看她有没有留下什么蛛丝马迹
see if she left any breadcrumbs behind.
在那见
Meet you there.
这儿什么都没有
There's nothing here.
对  看上去甲板好像被清理过
Yeah, it looks like the deck's been cleaned --
没有留下什么痕迹
There's no breadcrumbs.
除非
Unless...
她室友说
Her roommate said
船员会在船上藏东西
that the crew stashed things all over this ship.
万一这里是劳拉藏东西的地方呢
What if this was the spot where Lara kept her stash?
表演结束后她可能来到这
She could have come here after the show,
在船驶入港口前把那包毒品吞了进去
swallowed the bag before they put into port.
好吧  这儿什么地方能藏东西
Okay, so where do you hide something up here?
卡塞尔
Castle?
我们找到了犯罪现场
We found the crime scene.
凶手肯定是在这开枪打死了劳拉
Killer must have shot Lara here
然后把她的尸体抛进了海里
and then dumped her body overboard.
我们快没时间了
Okay, we are running out of time.
在被赶下船之前我们还有20分钟
We got 20 minutes before we're kicked off the ship for good.
好的  她被枪击中头部
All right, she was shot in the head,
应该会有更多血才对
so there should be a lot more blood.
这边
And there we go...
这儿有残留血迹
Blood residue right here.
看上去好像凶手在这留下了脚印
Looks like the killer tracked footprints through it.
你能把脚放在边上吗
Uh, you know, can you put your shoe against it,
当做比例尺
Just for scale?
你知道吗  我们真的应该坐一次邮轮
You know, we really - should take a little cruise.
想象一下我们能经历多少浪漫神秘的小插曲
Imagine all the romantic secret interludes we could have.
你是说像《泰坦尼克号》里面的场景
You mean like that scene in "Titanic,"
在老车子上的那一幕吗
the one in the old car?
对  杰克和罗斯还有起了水雾的窗户
Yeah, Jack and Rose and the steamy window.
我们可以跳进一艘救生艇里
We could just jump in one of these life boats.
救生艇
The life boats.
我不知道  卡塞尔  要进去貌似很难
I don't know, Castle. It would be tough to get in.
这里呢
What about right here?
卡塞尔
Castle.
那些肯定就是高纯海洛因
That must be the uncut heroin.
阿科斯塔  他们让你去B甲板
Hey, Acosta, they want you on "B" Deck.
我马上就去
I'll be right there.
谢天谢地他没看见我
Thank god he didn't see me.
我不知道怎么办
I don't know what to do.
我不能相信这船上的人
I can't trust anyone on the ship.
我要
I'll just...
我要拿些证据给警察
I'll grab some evidence for the cops.
那个肯定就是我们要找的毒贩
And that must be our drug dealer.
我想她在四处打探时发现了那些毒品
I bet she was snooping around and discovered those drugs.
她太害怕了不敢相信任何人
Except she was too scared to trust anyone,
所以就决定偷走一些样品
so she decided to smuggle out a sample.
她肯定在表演前把相机藏了起来
I bet she hid the camera before the show
之后又回来拿
and came back afterwards.
她没能回来
She never made it.
他肯定看到了她
He must have seen her.
表演结束后他跟踪她到这儿  把她杀了
He followed her after the show, and then he killed her.
我们要找到他
We got to find him.
还有15分钟
15 minutes.
-分头行动吗  -分头行动
- Divide and conquer? - Divide and conquer.
去找那些舞者  看她们是否认得他
Okay, go to the dancers. See if they know who he is.
我去操作甲板
I'll go to the operations deck.
不好意思  我找一下阿科斯塔
Um, excuse me, I'm looking for Acosta.
他就在下面
He's down there.
阿科斯塔  我得跟你谈谈
Acosta? We need to talk.
别动
Don't move.
你被捕了  罪名是杀害劳拉·麦登
You're under arrest - for the murder of Lara Madden.
他想找律师
So he wants an attorney.
公辩律师办公室正派人过来
The public defender's office is sending someone over now.
这家伙可真是劣迹斑斑
Yeah, this guy is dirty as hell.
他和洛斯哲塔斯贩毒集团有关联
He's connected - to the Los Zetas drug cartel.
看看我们在他那找到了什么
Well, look what we found on him.
他把他的猎物圈起来了
He circled his prey.
我是理查德·卡塞尔
This is Richard Castle.
你不是一个人喽
I take it that you're not alone.
当然不是
No, not at all.
你得回来一趟看看我找到的东西
You should probably make it back here I found something.
好的  待会见
All right, I'll see you soon.
对不起  各位  我先走一步
Sorry, guys. Got to take off.
里克
Hey, uh, Rick?
谢谢你今天帮忙
Thanks for today.
乐意效劳
My pleasure.
-贝克特  你有时间吗  -有
- Hey, Beckett, you got a second? - Uh, yeah.
我看了劳拉相机里剩下的录像
I watched the rest of the footage from Lara's camera.
看到的东西恶心  而且违法
What I saw was disgusting and criminal,
但都和毒品无关
but it had nothing to do with drugs.
她录下了
She was filming
邮轮船员非法向海里倾倒垃圾
cruise-shipworkers illegally dumping trash out at sea.
这才是她上操作甲板的原因
So that's why she was on the operations deck of the ship.
她在制作一部纪录片
She was making a documentary film.
这可怜的女孩想一个人做绿色和平组织
Poor thing was trying to be a one-woman greenpeace.
但她肯定偶然发现了通过船上垃圾
But she must have stumbled on a drug-smuggling conspiracy
运输海洛因的毒品走私阴谋
moving heroin through the cruise line's trash.
简直太聪明了
That's brilliant!
没人会去查港口进进出出的垃圾
Nobody looks into the trash moving in and out of ports.
所以我们现在要做的  就是通过传输途径
So all we got to do now is trace the pipeline
追回到那个中情局的神秘人
back to our mystery man inside the CIA.
好的  就从找出跟标志游轮公司
Okay, start by finding the trash-management company
签订合同的垃圾管理公司开始
contracted with Iconic cruise lines.
他们肯定参与了
Clearly, they're a part of this.
与此同时
In the meantime,
我去查查阿科斯塔是在给谁做事
I'm gonna try to figure out who Acosta's working for.
贝克特警监
Captain Beckett,
萨尔瓦多·阿科斯塔的公辩律师想找你谈谈
Salvador Acosta's public defender wants to have a word.
当然  请进
Uh, sure. Yeah, come on in.
贝克特警监  我是卡莱布·布朗
Hi, Captain Beckett. Caleb Brown.
你好  请坐
Hi. Please sit down.
我去查之前那条线索了
I'm gonna go work on the old core.
好的
Okay.
尽管我反对  阿科斯塔先生想做笔交易
So, against my advice, Mr. Acosta wants to make a deal.
他会接受二级谋杀的罪名
He'll cop to second-degree murder
如果你能够为他提出减刑的话
if you will recommend a reduced sentence.
二级谋杀罪  是吗
Second-degree murder, really?
为此他得给我们一些东西
He's gonna have to give us something for that.
好吧  比如说
Okay, like what?
比如他为谁做事那些海洛因从何而来
Like who he's working for and where the heroin came from.
什么海洛因
What -- what heroin?
律师  我们有录像
Counselor, we have - video footage
录下了你的委托人走私数公斤高纯海洛因
of your client smuggling kilos of uncut heroin.
警监  我的委托人坚称
Captain, my client insists
那些只是坏了的面粉
that those were merely bags of spoiled flour,
所以除非你有物证证明
So unless you can produce any physical evidence,
否则你也没法立案  所以
you don't really have a case, so...
好吧  这样
Okay, okay.
二级谋杀
Second-degree murder,
不减刑
no recommendation for a reduced sentence.
接受这个条件吧  警监
Take the win, Captain.
接受吧  因为我们并不真想上庭
Take it, 'cause we don't -- we don't want to go to trial.
我来猜猜  他想要做交易是吗
Ha, let me guess -- he offered you a deal?
是的  我跟他说我得再考虑一下
Yeah. I told him I had to think about it.
阿科斯塔不可能是单干
Well, there's no way Acosta was acting alone.
一个贩毒集团不可能会让那样一个家伙
No way a cartel would leave a guy like that
单独负责那么多的货
in charge of that much inventory.
我们现在终于有证据可以证明
Now we finally have the evidence to prove it.
鉴证组终于分析出你在犯罪现场
CSU finally analyzed that blood residue
拍下的血迹  看一下
from the photograph you took at the crime scene -- check it out.
在卡塞尔鞋子旁有两组不同的脚印
There's two different kinds of footprints next to Castle's shoe.
阿科斯塔在船上肯定有搭档
Acosta definitely had a partner aboard that ship.
我们得找出确凿证据让阿科斯塔招供
We need to find something solid to make Acosta roll.
我有他的的电话记录
You know, I have his cell records.
他给一个临时号码打了很多电话
There was a flurry of phone calls to a burner cell
就在杀人之前
right before the murder.
阿科斯塔可能是在跟他在船上的搭档进行协调
Acosta could have been coordinating with his partner on board the ship.
我会跟手机服务商联系
I'll get in touch with the cell provider,
看我们能否找到那个手机的信号以便定位
see if we can ping that burner phone so we can locate it.
仔细剖析阿科斯塔的生活
And take apart Acosta's life.
我们查一下已知同伙
Let's check known associates --
任何能够帮我们找出他搭档的线索
Anything that will point us to who his partner was.
我查到了是谁给凯特昨晚发的神秘短信
I found out who sent Kate that mystery text last night.
是维克拉姆
It was vikram.
等等  维克拉姆  我们认识的维克拉姆吗
Wait, Vikram? Our Vikram?
是的
Oh, yes.
这是什么
Well, what's this?
这是凯特和维克拉姆的手机之间
Oh, it's a secret messaging program
一个秘密的短信程序
between Kate and Vikram's cellphones.
通过代理服务器
It routes through proxy servers
发送到一个加密中央服务器
into an encrypted central server --
最先进的间谍工具
State-of-the-art spycraft.
但为什么呢  他们在做什么
But why? What are they up to?
我想问问你俩相同的问题
I could ask the same thing of the two of you.
理查德  怎么了
Richard, what's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
我跟你说过如果你做的事不能告诉你妈
I told you, if you can't tell your mother what you're doing,
这事你就不应该做
you should not be doing it.
是的  那是我八岁的时候
Yes, when I was 8.
就是
Well, exactly.
你现在应该更清楚这个道理
And you should know better by now.
我妻子有麻烦
My wife is in trouble.
我得知道到底是怎么回事
I have to know what's going on.
我得帮助她  我得保护她
I have to help her. I have to protect her.
不对  你得相信她
No, you have to trust her.
但事情终于有了眉目
But it's finally starting to make sense.
你难道不明白吗  妈妈
Don't you see, mother?
就在艾莉森·海德死后
Beckett broke up with me
贝克特跟我分了手
right after Allison Hyde's death.
也就是那时她和维克拉姆成了搭档
That's also when she partnered with Vikram.
所以我们就得问问自己
So we have to ask ourselves,
万一艾莉森·海德不是自杀呢
what if Allison Hyde didn't kill herself?
万一她是被人谋杀的呢
What if she was murdered?
就是
Yes.
凶手跟杀掉布莱肯参议员
By the same people who murdered Senator Bracken
及贝克特在总检察长办公室队友的是同一人
and Beckett's former team at the A.G.
维克拉姆之前就在总检察长办公室工作
And of course Vikram used to work at the A.G.'s office.
万一是凯特把他找来
What if Kate brought him in
是让他偷偷帮她调查这些谋杀案
to secretly help her investigate those murders?
你能破解维克拉姆的防火墙吗
Can you hack Vikram's firewall?
当然  但需要点时间
Sure. It'll take a while.
理查德
Richard...
听着  不管凯萨琳在做什么  为什么这么做
Look, regardless of what Katherine is doing and why,
你确定你想这样做吗
are you sure that you want to do this?
因为如果她发现你在暗中监视
Because if she finds out that you are spying,
你可能就已经跨过了不能反悔的界限
You may just have crossed a line you cannot uncross.
她可能会害死自己
She may just get herself killed.
她逼得我别无选择
She's left me no other choice.
总是有其他选择的
There's always another choice.
这事要怎么办  瑞克
So, what's it gonna be, Rick?
我必须知道真相  无论有什么后果
I have to know. No matter the consequence.
做吧
Do it.
阿科斯塔在凶杀案发生当晚
Hey, you know that burner cell
拨打的那个一次性电话
that Acosta called the night of the murder?
它刚通过一个信号塔发出了信号
It just pinged off a cell tower
位置在东哈莱姆125街和莱辛顿大道附近
at 125th and Lex in east Harlem.
阿科斯塔的同伙就在城里
Acosta's partner is in the city.
那怎么把他找出来
Now, how to find him?
他可能在信号塔方圆几英里内
He could be anywhere within a couple-mile radius
的任何地方
from that cell tower.
我们得深挖阿科斯塔的生活
We need to dig into Acosta's life,
看看他跟那个区域之前有没有交集
see if he had any connections to that part of town.
我告诉贝克特一声
I'll give Beckett the heads-up.
承包那条航线的垃圾清运公司
The trash company that contracts with the cruise line
名叫汤加群岛环卫公司
is called Friendly Islands Sanitation.
他们在拉美  加勒比地区和北非
They have satellites in Latin America, Caribbean,
都有分公司
and North Africa.
都是全球毒品交易的重点地区
Oh, key points in the worldwide drug trade.
一定是垃圾清运公司内部的什么人
So, somebody inside of the trash company
跟洛克塞特达成了一笔交易
must have cut a deal with Loksat
通过那道航线运送毒品
to move drugs through the cruise line.
那艘船在纽约一靠岸  劳拉拍到的海洛因
The heroin shipment Lara videotaped was offloaded with the trash
就跟着垃圾下船了  现在可能在任何地方
the minute the ship docked in new york -- it could be anywhere by now.
我们得跟着那些垃圾  看看它们都去了哪
Okay, we got to follow the garbage, see where it went.
这就办
On it.
是卡塞尔打来的
It's Castle.
不要接
Don't answer it.
瑞克  什么事
Hey, Rick. What's up?
你决定要买那艘船了吗
You decided to buy that boat?
某人听起来心情不错啊
Well, someone's in a good mood.
你是在想我们裸裎相对的时光吗
You thinking about our naked time?
呃  没有
Um...no.
我在想
Well, I am -- I haven't
事实上  我就没停下来过
stopped thinking about it, as a matter of fact.
我们今晚再来一轮怎么样  在我那儿
Um, tell you what, how about round two, tonight, my place?
别人都不会知道
No one has to know.
我不能去  我今晚得工作
Yeah, I can't. I have to work tonight.
我还以为当了警监
Um, well, I thought being a captain
你就可以把工作指派给别人了
meant you could delegate.
实际上我还是有些事需要自己做的
You know what? I actually have to do a few things myself.
说不定我能帮你  你在忙什么
Well, maybe I can help. What are you working on?
警监的工作
Um, captain stuff?
那个就
Well, that...
那祝愿你的警监工作一切顺利  拜拜
Then good luck with your captain stuff. Bye.
喂
Hello?
我们成功了
Yep. We got it.
她的手机信号就是我们穿过
Her cell signal was our trojan horse
维克拉姆第一道防火墙的木马
through Vikram's first firewall.
现在我就能一次黑进一台服务器
Now I can hack one server at a time
直到我找到他的核心服务器
until I find his central server.
后悔了
Second thoughts?
悔了好几次了
Second, third, fourth.
不了  我们  我们继续吧
No. Let's -- let's keep going.
还好吗
Everything all right?
挺好的  不过他有点怪怪的
Yeah, I mean, he was just a little weird.
他通常都很怪
Well, normally he's a lot weird, so...
是迷人的怪
In a charming kind of way.
看看这个
Oh. - check this out.
三个垃圾车
Three dump trucks
今天早晨从我们那艘邮轮上卸下了垃圾
offloaded trash from our cruise ship this morning.
三个都是早晨8:05分出发的
All three left at 8:05 A.M.,
但只有两辆车载9:17分出现在垃圾场
but only two showed up at the dump at 9:17.
所以第三辆车一定装着海洛因
So the third one must have been carrying the heroin,
送完货它才停回去
and then it stopped after it made the delivery.
但是送到了哪呢
But where?
我一直在查交通摄像头录像
I've been scrubbing traffic-cam footage,
但我在华盛顿高地跟丢了那辆垃圾车
but I lost the truck in Washington Heights.
尽可能找到关于那个卡车司机的一切资料
Pull everything we can on the truck driver.
警报  系统攻击
Alert -- system breach.
-我们有麻烦了  -什么
- Oh, we got a problem. - What?
有人在我的一个服务器里安插了一个木马
Someone synched a rat to one of my servers.
一个远程控制工具
A remote access tool --
我们正在被黑客攻击
we're being hacked.
-是洛克塞特干的吗  -我不知道
- By Loksat? - I don't know.
但我们一直很小心  他们是怎么找到我们的
But we've been so careful. How could they find us?
他们还没找到我们
They haven't found us yet,
只是击破了我们系统的外层
just cracked the outer layer of our system.
我要启动一个入侵检测程序
I'll start an intrusion inspection
看看是谁干的
and find out who our rat is.
-怎么了  -他们在查我们
- What? - They're onto us.
维克拉姆正在试着追踪我们的IP地址
Vikram's trying to track our I.P. Address.
你能阻止他吗
Can you stop him?
不能
No.
但我拖慢他
But I can slow him down.
攻击就是从城里某处发出的
It's coming from inside the city.
正在缩小范围
Trying to narrow it down.
这是什么乱七八糟的
What the hell?
你很厉害  但是我更厉害
Oh, you are good, but I am better.
猫咪视频  可不像洛克塞特做的事
Cat videos? That doesn't seem like Loksat.
谁会做这种事
Who would do that?
我们就快找到答案了
We're about to find out.
那个很难拖住他
That barely slowed him down.
我很抱歉  但他一分钟之内就会找到我们
I'm sorry, but he's gonna find us in less than a minute.
要放弃吗
Should we abort?
不  我们  我们就剩两个小亮盒子没进了
No. We -- we've only got two of the blinky boxes left to go.
-小亮盒子  -黑进去黑进去
- Blinky boxes? - Just hack, hack.
加油
Come on.
找到了
Got it.
那是卡塞尔的办公室
That's castle's office.
他一定是在和海莉合作
He must be working with Hayley.
她有技术能做到这一切
She's got the skill set for this,
她马上就要攻破我们的防火墙了
and she is about to breach our firewall.
如果她做到了  他们将立刻能拿到
If she does, - they'll have instant access
我们全部的调查资料
to our entire investigation.
不不不  那会让卡塞尔成为目标
No, no, no, no, that's gonna put a target on castle's back.
我们得阻止他
We have to stop him.
我能阻止他  但我需要时间
I can do it, but I need time.
我看看能不能帮你争取一些时间
Let me see if I can buy you some.
是贝克特来电话
It's Beckett calling.
是贝克特  她在给我打电话  我怎么办
That's beckett. She's calling. What do I do?
接电话  看看她知道了多少
Answer it. - let's see how much she knows.
宝贝
Hey, babe.
对今晚的安排改主意了
Change your mind about tonight?
今晚还是不行
Tonight's still not gonna work.
但现在怎么样
But what about right now?
去你办公室起水雾吧
Feel like steaming up your office?
我办公室  听起来棒极了
My office? That sounds great.
我正在
I'm, uh...
现在正在办一些事情
Sort of in the middle of something right now.
是吗  那真不巧  因为我就在楼下呢
Really? That's too bad, 'cause I'm right downstairs.
是楼下  真的楼下是吧
Downstairs downstairs?
是啊  我10秒钟就能上楼
Yeah. I can be up in 10 seconds.
10秒可真不长啊
10 seconds is not long at all.
等  等  等一下
Hang -- hang -- hang on one second.
我们得关掉它
We've got to shut it down.
她就快要进门了
She's gonna walk in the front door.
不  她在说谎
No. She's lying.
她的电话信号在皇后区呢
Her phone is pinging from Queens.
她知道是我们在攻击他们
She knows it's us who's hacking her.
刚刚抱歉啦  我正在脱裤子
Sorry about that. Just taking off my pants.
你上来吗
You coming up?
他知道我在说谎
He knows I'm lying.
你知道吗
You know what?
刚刚发生了点事情
Something just came up.
下回再说
Rain check?
没问题  你知道上哪找我
Sure. You know where to find me.
她就快攻进来了
She's almost in.
我可以发出一个网络炸弹
I could launch a cyber nuke,
但它会完全摧毁他的系统
but it will completely fry his system.
他在家里放了一个备用系统
He's got a back-up system at home.
所以确定要放炸弹吗
Is that a go for launch?
是的
Yes.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no! Oh!
刚刚发生了什么
What just happened?
恐怕这是终极毁灭了
Armageddon, I'm afraid.
维克拉姆刚刚炸掉了我们整个系统
Vikram just nuked the whole system.
我们失去了一切
We've lost everything.
我们失去了
We've l--
我从来就不喜欢那家伙
I never liked that guy.
他们进去了吗
Did they get in?
没有  再晚一秒他们就进去了
No. Another second and they would have.
谢天谢地我们的地址和文件都很安全
Thankfully, our location and all our files are still safe.
只是暂时安全
Yeah, for now.
我只希望我刚才没炸毁了我的婚姻
I just hope I didn't nuke my marriage.
你去哪
Where you going?
我得跟卡塞尔谈谈
I need to talk to Castle.
不  你得等等再谈
No, that'll have to wait.
我找到了汤加群岛环卫公司那个垃圾车司机
I found the garbage-truck driver from Friendly Islands.
他还有30分钟就下班了
His shift ends in 30 minutes.
现在新闻上都是劳拉的凶杀案
With Lara's murder all over the news,
他们可能会加强防卫  我们现在就得找到他
they might be circling their wagons -- we got to get to him now.
不  我讨厌向他说谎
No, I hate lying to him.
我明白  但你是因为正确的理由才这么做的
I know, but you're doing it for the right reasons.
这是我们第一次真正接近洛克塞特的机会
This is our first real shot to get to Loksat.
我们得抓住
We have to take it.
你说的对
You're right.
跟我讲讲那个司机的情况
Tell me about the driver.
他叫萨姆·麦基
His name is Sam Mackey.
等等  等一下
Wait, wait! Wait!
求你们不要伤害我  你们是什么人
Please don't hurt me! Please! Who are you?
当你搞砸了一单运输的时候  我们就会出现
We're the people that show when you screw up a delivery.
不  我直接去仓库了  完全按照指示做的
No, I took it straight to the warehouse, just like I was told.
别骗我们  我们都看见了
Don't lie to us. We were watching.
-你并没按照指示来做  -不  我做了
- You didn't follow instructions. - Yes, I did.
我直接去了布朗克斯区的那个地方
I went straight to the place in the Bronx
经过三号大道桥
by the 3rd Avenue Bridge,
按照巴拿马那个人说得一样
just like the guy from Panama said!
你看见什么了吗
Did you see anything?
没有
No.
他让我待在卡车里  我照做了
I stayed in the truck like I was told.
巴拿马那个人是谁
Who's the guy in Panama?
我不知道
I don't know.
我知道你在想什么  萨姆
I know what you're thinking, Sam.
你认为我不会杀了你  你想得没错
You're thinking I'm not gonna kill you, and you are right.
但你一直在经营毒品生意
But you've been running drugs,
那就意味着纽约警局可以没收你的全部财产
and that means the NYPD can seize everything in your life.
想让你的孩子们住在纸盒箱里吗
Want your kids to live out of a cardboard box?
你不配合  结果就会是那样
'Cause that's what's gonna happen.
我不知道任何名字
I don't know any names.
他们付钱给我  不让我多问
They pay me not to ask questions.
别扯上我的家人  我...
Don't involve my family -- I-I...
我没有选择的余地
I didn't have a choice.
我想他说得是实话
I think he's telling the truth.
好吧  萨姆  接下来这样
All right, Sam, here's what's gonna happen.
我不会逮捕你
I'm not gonna arrest you,
但如果你接到新的货物  就打这个号码
but if you get another delivery, you call this number.
不  不行  我不能  他们会杀了我
No, no, no, no. I can't. They'll kill me.
他们也许会杀了你
They might.
但如果我逮捕你  他们绝对会杀了你
But if I arrest you, they definitely will.
如果你敢把这段对话告诉他们
And telling them about this conversation
我保证你再也见不到你的家人
guarantees that your whole family will be wiped out.
我什么也不会说的  我保证
I won't say a word. I promise.
很好  那装满海洛因的仓库到底在哪
Good. Now, where exactly is the warehouse full of heroin?
我们来晚了  海洛因已经被运走了
We're too late. They already moved the heroin.
而且外面没有摄像头
And there's no street cams outside
没法得知谁把货物运走的
so we could see who picked it up.
见鬼  什么线索也没有
Damn it. This was for nothing.
不  我们有线索的
No, no, we do have something.
我们知道谁是汤加群岛环卫的
We find out who the main players are
主要头目了
at Friendly Islands Sanitation,
萨姆下一次运货时
and the next time Sam catches a shipment,
我们会  我们会在那的
we'll -- we'll be there.
是莱恩
It's Ryan.
好的  我马上就到
Okay. Yeah. I-I'll be right there.
他们似乎找到阿科斯塔的同伙了
They think they found Acosta's partner.
阿科斯塔神秘同伙所用手机
Cellphone belonging to Acosta's mystery partner
今天早些时候在东哈林区被使用过
was used in East Harlem earlier today.
我们彻查了阿科斯塔
We tore apart Acosta's life.
他过去常在那个街区的一处公寓里过夜
He used to crash at an apartment in that neighborhood.
房租上的名字是里奥·朗加佐
The name on the lease was a Leo Longarzo.
里奥是厄瓜多尔
Leo is a traveling salesman
一间进出口公司的旅行推销员
for an Ecuadorian import/export company.
那听起来很像贩毒集团头目的代号
Well, that sounds like code for a Cartel Lieutenant.
没错  他周游世界  无妻无子
Right. He travels all over the world, no wife, no kids.
更像了
It gets better.
我们查了巡航的旅客名单
We checked the passenger manifest of the cruise.
朗加佐在那艘船上
Longarzo was on that ship.
他就是我们要找的人
That's our guy.
很好  派警员到他公寓附近守着
All right, send uniforms to sit on his apartment.
看他是否会出现
See if he turns up.
好的
All right.
凯特  我们得谈谈
Kate? We need to talk.
知道吗  当我挂上私家侦探的招牌时
You know, when I hung up my shingle as a P.I.,
还以为只会去跟踪一些妻子
I knew I would have to follow some wives.
从没想到会跟踪自己的妻子
I just never thought it would be my own.
卡塞尔  你为什么就不能相信我呢
Castle, why couldn't you just trust me?
你怎么能那样要求我呢
How can you ask me that?
昨晚我看到维克拉姆发给你的信息了
I saw the text Vikram sent you last night.
我以为你有麻烦了
I thought you were in trouble.
结果却发现你一直在欺骗我
Instead, I find out you've been lying to me.
我只是想保护你
I was trying to protect you.
躲避杀害艾莉森·海德的凶手吗
From Allison Hyde's killer?
是的  当我意识到你并不是想独处时
Yeah, it was easy to figure out once I realized
我很容易就查出来了
you weren't just looking for "Me" time.
洛克塞特认为他成功瞒过去了
LokSat thinks that his cover-up worked.
所以他才放过我们的
That's why he let us live.
如果他发现我还在追查此事
And if he finds out that I am still pursuing this,
他会杀了我和我身边的任何人
he will kill me and anyone that I am close to.
所以我必须让你离开我
That's why I had to push you away.
单是你有那样的想法就让我心碎
The fact that you even think that breaks my heart.
为了你我愿意赴汤蹈火  凯特
I'd walk into a tornado for you, Kate.
如果失去你  我会死的
And I would die if I lost you.
你想知道什么才最伤人吗
You want to know what hurts the most?
你本可以告诉我全部真相
You could have come to me with everything,
像你之前做得那样离开我
broken us up just like you did,
但只把那当做掩饰
only it would have been a cover.
而暗地里在一起  我们可以打败那个人的
And together, in secret, we could have taken this guy down.
只是你从没那样想过
Only that thought never even occurred to you,
因为内心深处  你喜欢做破碎的人
because deep down inside, you like being broken,
而你需要这样的执念
and you need this obsession.
无论我怎么做  都无法改变
And no matter what I do, I can't change that.
只有你能  凯特
Only you can, Kate.
警员发现阿科斯塔的同伙
Hey, uniforms just spotted Acosta's partner
正进入他的公寓
going into his building.
我们要去抓他
We're gonna go roust him.
不过你不去也行
But we can roll without you.
没事  反正我也要走了
No, actually, I was just leaving.
等等  卡塞尔
Wait, no, Castle.
你有工作要做
You have a job to do.
没人比你做得更好
And there's no one better.
朗加佐大约四十分钟前进去的
Longarzo came in about 40 minutes ago.
-跟别人一起吗  -不  就他自己
- Anybody with him? - No, he's alone.
而且据我所知  公寓里
And there's no one else in the apartment
并没有其他人
as far as I can tell.
好的  剩下的交给我们吧  谢谢你
All right, we'll take it from here. Thank you.
如果这人真的是贩毒集团的人
If this guy really is Cartel,
那间公寓里一定有武器
he might have an arsenal up in that apartment.
是不是该叫紧急应急小组来
Should we call ESU?
纽约警局
NYPD!
别跑
Hey! Stop!
下来
Get down!
枪
Gun!
不
No!
-你还好吗  -不好
- You okay? - No.
阿科斯塔的同伙本可以让我们接近洛克塞特
Acosta's partner could have brought us closer to LokSat.
结果他却躺在了停尸间
Instead, he's in the morgue.
这一切都在我眼皮子底下崩塌了
It's all come crashing down around my ears,
而我却只能怪自己
and I've got nobody to blame but myself.
你要在这自怨自艾
Ah, you are having a pity party.
完全可以  我走
That's okay. I'll leave.
但我可能找到了一个非常好的线索
But I will be taking a pretty juicy clue with me.
如果你敢耍我  我会开枪打你的
If you're messing with me, I might shoot you.
想知道我发现了什么吗
Does that mean you want to hear what I got?
当然
Yeah.
好吧
Okay. Okay.
我追踪到了萨姆·麦基藏匿海洛因
I was able to trace the ownership of the warehouse
那个仓库的拥有者
where Sam Mackey dropped off the heroin.
是保时捷控股的一间公司
It's a Cayman's shell corp.
我又深挖了一下从1999年至今的公司文件
I dug back into the articles of incorporation from '99.
你绝不会相信那些文件是谁写的
You won't believe - who wrote up those documents.
卡莱布·布朗
Caleb Brown.
阿科斯塔的公共辩护律师吗
Acosta's public defender?
结果发现布朗过去任职于一间
Turns out Brown worked for a major corporate law firm
大型律师事务所
back in the day.
每年收入都在50万美元左右
Pulled in mid-six figures annually.
然后他几年前突然辞职了
Then he suddenly gave it up a few years ago
给人当起了辩护律师
to be a defender of the people.
那是个完美的掩护身份
That's the perfect cover.
这让布朗可以接触到狱中的贩毒成员
It gives Brown access to assets in prison
让他可以为那些
and allows him to pass orders
已经被抓获的毒贩下达命令
to dealers that we've already caught.
像阿科斯塔那样的毒贩
Dealers like Acosta.
布朗让阿科斯塔顶下谋杀劳拉的罪行
Brown told Acosta to take the fall for Lara's murder
这样我们就不会再追查毒品
so that we would back off of the drugs.
而阿科斯塔照做了  布朗就是这么厉害
And Acosta obliged. That's how powerful Brown is.
好吧  我们不能直接去找这个人
Okay, we can't go straight at this guy.
他不是吓坏的卡车司机  他是头鲨鱼
He's not a scared truck driver. This guy is a shark.
他若知道我们找上他  洛克塞特会灭了我们
And if he sees us coming, LokSat's gonna burn all of us.
我们必须暗地里追查布朗的行踪
We've got to track Brown's every move nice and quiet.
这会花点时间
It's gonna take time.
是的  但如果我们做得好...
Yeah, but if we do it right...
他会直接带我们找到洛克赛特
He'll lead us straight to LokSat.
我以为你说撒谎是不对的
I thought you said lying was wrong.
没错  可是...
I did. It is, but...
她认为她在保护我
She thought she was protecting me.
好吧  那意思是你原谅她了吗
Okay, so does that mean you could forgive her?
我不知道  也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
好吧  别误会我的意思  里克
Yeah, don't take this the wrong way, Rick,
但你的话毫无意义
but you don't make any sense.
那是因为我深爱着她
Well, that's because I'm in love.
但你是不会明白的
But you wouldn't understand that.
那你为什么要跟我说这些呢
So why are you talking to me about it?
问得好
Touche.
你说得对
You were right.
好吧
Okay.
你说得每一句话都是对的
Everything that you said, you were absolutely right.
能再具体一点吗
Could you be more specific?
我们本可以把分手作为掩饰
That our break-up - could have just been a cover
这样我们就能联手扳倒洛克赛特
so that we could bring down LokSat together.
是的
Yeah.
我希望你那时能来找我
I wish you would have come to me.
现在我来了...
Well, I'm here now...
我们来吧
So let's do it.
并不是那么简单的
It's not that easy.
我以为你会...
I thought that you would --
会原谅你  无视你曾经让我经历过的痛苦吗
Just take you back, in spite of what you put me through?
卡塞尔  对不起  我恨自己伤害了你
Look, Castle, I am sorry. I hate that I hurt you.
那从不是我希望的结果
That was never what I wanted.
但你的确伤害我了  凯特  而更糟的是...
But you did hurt me, Kate, and what's worse...
-你对我失去信心了  -不  我从没...
- You lost faith in me. - No, I never --
我需要你  里克
I need you, Rick.
在这件事发生前  我从未想到
I didn't realize even how much I needed you
自己会如此需要你
until this happened.
求你  别让我独自经历这些
Please, just don't make me do this without you.
好吧
Okay.
但你知道
Though you do realize
我必须先惩罚你一下
I'm gonna have to punish you a little first.
裸体惩罚吗
Naked punishing?
赤裸裸的惩罚
Very naked punish.
人人美剧「在线播放」
震撼上线
欢迎前往苹果商店
及各大安卓市场下载人人美剧客户端
你们俩啊
Aw, you guys.